Finding Aid for the Recordings of Creative Associates Recitals, 1964-1980
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Reel to reel tapes, 1964-1980, I.; Reel 1-Reel 172
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 65, March 29, 1972, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 9, Reel 097-098)
    Performers: Roberto Laneri, clarinet; George Perle, piano
    Duration: 12:07
    Cassette backup: CA 359
    Work number: ubmu0063_098_01
    Kondo, Jo
    Summer Days (1970)
    Duration: 11:41
    Cassette backup: CA 360
    Work number: ubmu0063_098_02
    Schiaffini, Giancarlo
    No Insistence Upon Compositional Values (1972)
    Performers: Roberto Laneri, clarinet; Paula Greenbaum, Adrienne Tworek, voices; Jeffery Kowalsky, percussion
    Duration: 13:08
    Cassette backup: CA 361
    Work number: ubmu0063_098_03
    Laneri, Roberto
    Esorcismi No. 1 (1972)
    Performers: Roberto Laneri, clarinet, Julius Eastman, voice; Lynn Harbold, percussion; Jesse Levine, viola; Donald Miller, trombone
    Duration: 26:30
    Cassette backup: CA 362
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 66, April 10, 1972, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 9, Reel 099)
    Work number: ubmu0063_099_01
    S.E.M. Ensemble
    S.E.M. gives a lecture
    Performers: S.E.M. Ensemble: Petr Kotik, Julius Eastman, Roberto Laneri, Jan Williams
    Duration: 53:33
    Cassette backup: CA 363
    Work number: ubmu0063_099_02
    There is Singularly Nothing (1971) (Group improvisation)
    Performers: Petr Kotik, Julius Eastman, Roberto Laneri, Jan Williams
    Duration: 21:03
    Cassette backup: CA 364
    Note: Might be performed simultaneously with Julius Eastman's Eine kleine Nachtmusik.
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 67, May 4, 1972, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 9, Reel 100)
    Work number: ubmu0063_100_01
    Schoenberg, Arnold
    Herzgewachse, op. 20 (1911)
    Performers: Judith Kerman, soprano; Mario Falcao, harp; James Whitman, harmonium; William Appleby, celesta
    Duration: 3:49
    Cassette backup: CA 365
    Work number: ubmu0063_100_02
    Herzgewachse, op. 20 (1911) (repeat)
    Duration: 3:56
    Cassette backup: CA 365a
    Note: Second performance.
    Work number: ubmu0063_100_03
    Stiller, Andrew Philip
    Cadres and Communes (1969)
    Performers: Andrew Stiller, bassoon
    Cassette backup: CA 366
    Work number: ubmu0063_100_04
    Sonata, flutes (2), op. 2, no. 1, G major
    Performers: Andrew Stiller, James Furdell, alto recorders
    Duration: 13:25
    Cassette backup: CA 367
    Work number: ubmu0063_100_05
    Quartet (1965)
    Performers: Judith Kerman, soprano; Jay Beckenstein, saxophone; Andrew Stiller, bassoon; Beye Fyfe, horn; Lee Lovallo, trombone; Wendell Hauer, violoncello; Jeffery Kowalsky, percussion; William Appleby, keyboards
    Duration: 9:19
    Cassette backup: CA 368
    Work number: ubmu0063_100_06
    Sonata, clarinet
    Performers: Andrew Stiller, clarinet
    Duration: 4:53
    Cassette backup: CA 369
    Work number: ubmu0063_100_07
    Anonymous (14th century)
    Trotto
    Performers: Andrew Stiller, soprano recorder; Christopher Coover, lute; Jeffery Kowalsky, percussion
    Duration: 1:11
    Cassette backup: CA 371
    Work number: ubmu0063_100_08
    McDonald, Country Joe
    Acid Commercial (1967)
    Performers: The Ad-Hoc Trystereo System Jug Band
    Duration: 1:01
    Cassette backup: CA 372
    Work number: ubmu0063_100_09
    Gesti (1966)
    Performers: Andrew Stiller, alto recorder
    Duration: 5:51
    Cassette backup: CA 370
    Work number: ubmu0063_100_10
    Quintet for Bass Instruments (1966)
    Performers: Amrom Chodos, contra-alto clarinet; Jay Beckenstein, bass saxophone, Andrew Stiller, bassoon; Lee Lovallo, trombone; Jeffery Kowalsky, timpani
    Duration: 10:17
    Cassette backup: CA 373
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 68, October 18, 1972, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 9, Reel 101-102)
    Work number: ubmu0063_101_01
    Eastman, Julius
    Comp 1 (1971)
    Performers: Petr Kotik, flute
    Cassette backup: CA 374
    Work number: ubmu0063_101_02
    There Is Singularly Nothing no. 1 (1971)
    Duration: 32:36
    Cassette backup: CA 376
    Work number: ubmu0063_102_01
    Atlas Eclipticalis (1961) and Fontana Mix (1958)
    Duration: 30:27
    Cassette backup: CA 377A-B
    Work number: ubmu0063_102_02
    Young, La Monte
    Composition No. 9 (1960)
    Duration: 4:14
    Cassette backup: CA 375
    Note: Order in original inventory differs. Check content.
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 69, November 11, 1972, 1 10-inch reel; Full-track mono, 7.5 ips (Box 9, Reel 103)
    Work number: ubmu0063_103_01
    Martino, Donald
    Parisonatina Al'Dodecafonia, op. 37 (1964)
    Performers: David Gibson, violoncello
    Duration: 10:51
    Cassette backup: CA 378
    Work number: ubmu0063_103_02
    Wyner, Yehudi
    De Novo (1971)
    Performers: John Burgess, flute; Amrom Chodos, bass clarinet; David Gibson, violoncello; Louis Bruno, double bass; Henry Rubin, Diane Williams, violas; Jan Williams, conductor
    Cassette backup: CA 379
    Work number: ubmu0063_103_03
    Gibson, David R
    Thirteen Ways of Looking at a Blackbird (1971)
    Performers: Julius Eastman, voice; Henry Rubin, violin; Diane Williams, viola; David Gibson, violoncello; Jeffery Kowalsky, piano; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 23:05
    Cassette backup: CA 380
    Work number: ubmu0063_103_04
    Durations 2 (1960)
    Performers: David Gibson, violoncello; Jeffery Kowalsky, piano
    Duration: 9:36
    Cassette backup: CA 381
    Work number: ubmu0063_103_05
    Suite, violoncello alone, no. 6, BWV 1012, D major
    Duration: 29:22
    Cassette backup: CA 382
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 70, December 15, 1972, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 10, Reel 104)
    Work number: ubmu0063_104_01
    Fantasy pieces for piano Solo
    Performers: David Del Tredici, piano
    Cassette backup: CA 383
    Work number: ubmu0063_104_02
    Songs to texts of James Joyce (1959)
    Performers: Winifred Black, soprano; David Del Tredici, piano
    Duration: 13:01
    Cassette backup: CA 384
    Work number: ubmu0063_104_03
    Helps, Robert
    Three Etudes (1959)
    Duration: 6:35
    Cassette backup: CA 385
    Work number: ubmu0063_104_04
    Sensitivo per Arco Solo (1959)
    Cassette backup: CA 386
    Work number: ubmu0063_104_05
    Three fragments for Cello and piano (1970)
    Duration: 5:18
    Cassette backup: CA 387
    Work number: ubmu0063_104_06
    Performers: David Gibson, violoncello; Stephen Manes, piano
    Duration: 21:38
    Cassette backup: CA 388
    Work number: ubmu0063_104_07
    Projection I (1950)
    Duration: 6:55
    Cassette backup: CA 389
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 71, January 31, 1973, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 10, Reel 105)
    Work number: ubmu0063_105_01
    1 Finger Exercise (1971)
    Performers: Amrom Chodos, clarinet
    Duration: 4:08
    Cassette backup: CA 390
    Work number: ubmu0063_105_02
    B,a,b,b,it,t (1966)
    Cassette backup: CA 391
    Work number: ubmu0063_105_03
    Smith, Williams Overton
    Suite (1952)
    Performers: Henry Rubin, violin; Amrom Chodos, clarinet
    Duration: 15:13
    Cassette backup: CA 392
    Work number: ubmu0063_105_04
    Piece in Two Parts (1961/1962) for Six Players
    Performers: Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Henry Rubin, violin; Gerald Soffer, trumpet; David Gibson, violoncello; Suzanne Thomas, harp; Stephen Manes, piano
    Cassette backup: CA 393
    Work number: ubmu0063_105_05
    Performers: Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Dennis Kahle, percussion
    Duration: 13:44
    Cassette backup: CA 394
    Work number: ubmu0063_105_06
    Sonata, clarinet, piano, op. 120, no. 1, F minor
    Performers: Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Stephen Manes, piano
    Duration: 23:18
    Cassette backup: CA 395
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 72, February 21, 1973, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 10, Reel 106)
    Work number: ubmu0063_106_01
    Sonata, violin, piano
    Cassette backup: CA 396
    Work number: ubmu0063_106_02
    Cassette backup: CA 397
    Work number: ubmu0063_106_03
    Fragment no. 5 for Viola and Vibraphone
    Performers: Henry Rubin, viola; Dennis Kahle, vibraphone
    Duration: 15:12
    Cassette backup: CA 398
    Work number: ubmu0063_106_04
    Andri, George
    Five pieces for Violin and percussion
    Performers: Henry Rubin, violin; Jeffery Kowalsky, percussion
    Duration: 10:03
    Cassette backup: CA 399
    Work number: ubmu0063_106_05
    Tzigane
    Duration: 10:02
    Cassette backup: CA 400
    Work number: ubmu0063_106_06
    Gluck, Christoph Willibald
    Orfeo ed Euridice. Dance of the Blessed Spirits, arranged
    Duration: 4:12
    Cassette backup: CA 401
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 73, March 7, 1973, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 10, Reel 107-108)
    Work number: ubmu0063_107_01
    Klucevsek, Guy
    Interspace (1972)
    Performers: Dennis Kahle, percussion; Jeffery Kowalsky, percussion, keyboards
    Duration: 11:15
    Cassette backup: CA 402
    Work number: ubmu0063_107_02
    George, Ron
    Music for a Favorite Person (1968, rev. 1970)
    Duration: 13:59
    Cassette backup: CA 403
    Work number: ubmu0063_107_03
    Torcaso, Enrico
    Refractions (1972)
    Performers: David Gibson, violoncello; Richard Trythall, piano; Dennis Kahle, percussion
    Duration: 11:58
    Cassette backup: CA 404
    Work number: ubmu0063_107_04
    Kahle, Dennis E.
    Third Beat of Nothing (1972, rev. 1973)
    Performers: David Sussman, guitar; Dennis Kahle, Jeffery Kowalsky, Jan Williams, percussion
    Duration: 10:16
    Cassette backup: CA 405
    Work number: ubmu0063_108_01
    North (1971)
    Performers: Charlene English, Dan Buciur, saxophone; Jeffery Kowalsky, piano, percussion; Robert Bolt, Amrom Chodos, Michael Wellen, Jan Williams, percussion
    Duration: 27:53
    Cassette backup: CA 406
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 74, April 5, 1973, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 10, Reel 109)
    Work number: ubmu0063_109_01
    Sonata, piano, no. 2
    Duration: 42:38
    Cassette backup: CA 407
    Work number: ubmu0063_109_02
    Trythall, Richard
    Coincidences (1969)
    Duration: 9:25
    Cassette backup: CA 408
    Work number: ubmu0063_109_03
    Verse (Concert version 1972). Spoken introduction
    Performers: Tape realized by the composer
    Cassette backup: CA 409
    Note: Only the introduction recorded.
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 75, May 16, 1973, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 10, Reel 110)
    Work number: ubmu0063_110_01
    Gabrieli, Andrea
    Ricercare del 12o Tono
    Performers: Lee Lovallo, trombone; James Whitman, organ; Andrew Stiller, tenor shawm
    Duration: 2:59
    Cassette backup: CA 410
    Work number: ubmu0063_110_02
    Obrecht, Jacob
    Canon (published by Glareanus 1547)
    Performers: Lee Lovallo, trombone; Andrew Stiller, tenor shawm
    Duration: 1:42
    Cassette backup: CA 411
    Work number: ubmu0063_110_03
    Canzona da Sonare a l, no. 4 (1634)
    Performers: Andrew Stiller, alto recorder; James Whitman, organ; Wendell Haver, violoncello
    Duration: 4:25
    Cassette backup: CA 412
    Work number: ubmu0063_110_04
    Performers: Andrew Stiller, alto recorder; James Whitman, harpsichord; Wendell Haver, violoncello
    Cassette backup: CA 413
    Work number: ubmu0063_110_05
    Musica ungetutscht (1972)
    Performers: Jeffery Kowalsky, vibraphone; James Whitman, piano; Andrew Stiller, bassoon
    Cassette backup: CA 414
    Work number: ubmu0063_110_06
    Trio, piano, clarinet, viola, K. 498, E-flat major
    Performers: Andrew Stiller, clarinet; Delmar Stewart, viola; James Whitman, piano
    Duration: 23:27
    Cassette backup: CA 415
    Work number: ubmu0063_110_07
    Pierrot Solaire: Songs and Melodramas for a Time of Change on Texts of Diane di Prima (1972)
    Performers: Jane Holcombe, voice; Frina Arschanska Boldt, keyboards
    Duration: 26:58
    Cassette backup: CA 416
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 76, September 25, 1973, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 10, Reel 111)
    Work number: ubmu0063_111_01
    Gibson, David R.
    Fragment No. 4 for Three Trumpets, Clarinet, Vibraphone and Double Bass
    Performers: David Kuehn, Gerald Soffer, Ronald Mendola, trumpets; Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Robert Bolt, vibraphone; Louis Bruno, double bass
    Duration: 8:26
    Cassette backup: CA 417
    Work number: ubmu0063_111_02
    Embellishments No. 2 for String Quartet (1972)
    Performers: Benjamin Hudson, Carol Zeavin, violins; Delmar Stewart, viola; David Gibson, violoncello
    Cassette backup: CA 418
    Work number: ubmu0063_111_03
    From the 14th on (1973)
    Duration: 12:59
    Cassette backup: CA 419
    Work number: ubmu0063_111_04
    Lion's Head (1973)
    Performers: David Gibson, double bass
    Cassette backup: CA 420
    Work number: ubmu0063_111_05
    Drew, James
    Maze Maker (1969)
    Duration: 10:34
    Cassette backup: CA 421
    Work number: ubmu0063_111_06
    Shadows (1973)
    Performers: Jan Williams, Paul Mouradian, Dennis Kahle, percussion
    Duration: 20:45
    Cassette backup: CA 422
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 77, November 28, 1973, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 10, Reel 112)
    Work number: ubmu0063_112_01
    Sigurbjornsson, Thorkell
    Intrada for clarinet, viola and piano
    Performers: Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Delmar Stewart, viola; Thorkell Sigurbjornsson, piano
    Cassette backup: CA 423
    Work number: ubmu0063_112_02
    Oft vex Leikur Af Litlu for Violoncello and piano
    Performers: David Gibson, violoncello; Thorkell Sigurbjornsson, piano
    Duration: 6:44
    Cassette backup: CA 424
    Work number: ubmu0063_112_03
    Sveinsson, Atli Heimir
    Mengi
    Performers: Thorkell Sigurbjornsson, piano
    Duration: 9:50
    Cassette backup: CA 425
    Work number: ubmu0063_112_04
    Hasselby-Quartet
    Duration: 11:33
    Cassette backup: CA 426
    Work number: ubmu0063_112_05
    Mild und (mesitens) leise
    Cassette backup: CA 427
    Work number: ubmu0063_112_06
    Kisum for Clarinet, Viola and piano
    Duration: 31:24
    Cassette backup: CA 428
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 78, January 23, 1974, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 10, Reel 113)
    Work number: ubmu0063_113_01
    Otte, Hans
    Text (1973)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute
    Duration: 4:16
    Cassette backup: CA 429
    Work number: ubmu0063_113_02
    Dohl, Friedheim
    Textur I (1971)
    Cassette backup: CA 430
    Work number: ubmu0063_113_03
    Engelmann, Hans Ulrich
    Variante (1960)
    Cassette backup: CA 431
    Work number: ubmu0063_113_04
    Zimmermann, Bernd Alois
    Tempus Loquendi … (1963)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute, alto flute, bass flute
    Duration: 10:04
    Cassette backup: CA 432
    Work number: ubmu0063_113_05
    Variations II (1961)
    Duration: 8:06
    Cassette backup: CA 433
    Work number: ubmu0063_113_06
    Fukushima, Kazuo
    Mei (1962)
    Cassette backup: CA 434
    Work number: ubmu0063_113_07
    Soegijo, Paul Gutama
    Saih I (1970)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute and voice
    Duration: 12:38
    Cassette backup: CA 435
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 79, March 13, 1974, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 10, Reel 114)
    Work number: ubmu0063_114_01
    Sonata, viola da gamba, harpsichord, BWV 1027, G major
    Performers: Delmar Stewart, viola da gamba; David Fuller, harpsichord
    Duration: 15:54
    Cassette backup: CA 436
    Work number: ubmu0063_114_02
    Scoville, Margaret
    Piece (1974)
    Performers: Toshiko Kohno, flute; Delmar Stewart, viola; Bronislava Humek Melandinidis, piano
    Duration: 7:51
    Cassette backup: CA 437
    Work number: ubmu0063_114_03
    Sonata, arpeggione, piano, D. 821, arranged
    Performers: Delmar Stewart, viola; Bronislava Humek Melandinidis, piano
    Duration: 24:21
    Cassette backup: CA 438
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 80, April 20, 1974, 1 10-inch reel; Full-track mono, 7.5 ips (Box 11, Reel 115)
    Work number: ubmu0063_115_01
    Copland, Aaron
    Performers: Benjamin Hudson, violin; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Duration: 20:23
    Cassette backup: CA 439
    Work number: ubmu0063_115_02
    440 (1973)
    Performers: Julius Eastman, voice; Benjamin Hudson, violin; Maureen Gallagher, viola; James Van Demark, double bass
    Duration: 22:52
    Cassette backup: CA 440
    Note: With spoken introduction by Julius Eastman.
    Note: The Eastman piece has distortion on source tape.
    Work number: ubmu0063_115_03
    Ysaye, Eugene
    Sonata, violin alone, op. 27, no. 3
    Performers: Benjamin Hudson, violin
    Cassette backup: CA 441
    Work number: ubmu0063_115_04
    Enesco, Georges
    Sonata, violin, piano, no. 3, op. 25, A minor
    Duration: 26:12
    Cassette backup: CA 442
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 81, May 15, 1974, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 11, Reel 116)
    Work number: ubmu0063_116_01
    Set for Clarinet (1954)
    Duration: 9:18
    Cassette backup: CA 443
    Work number: ubmu0063_116_02
    New Creature (1974)
    Performers: Ronald Richards, Paul Schlossman, English horns; Amrom Chodos, Andrew Stiller, alto clarinets
    Duration: 8:44
    Cassette backup: CA 444
    Work number: ubmu0063_116_03
    Bozza, Eugene
    Epithalme (1971)
    Duration: 6:22
    Cassette backup: CA 445
    Work number: ubmu0063_116_04
    Joplin, Scott
    Entertainer Rag, arranged
    Duration: 4:48
    Cassette backup: CA 446
    Work number: ubmu0063_116_05
    Performers: Rachel Lewis, soprano; Amrom Chodos, clarinet
    Duration: 5:01
    Cassette backup: CA 447
    Work number: ubmu0063_116_06
    Quintet, clarinet string, op. 115, B minor
    Performers: Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Benjamin Hudson, Carol Zeavin, violins; Maureen Gallagher, viola; Dana Rusinak, violoncello
    Duration: 36:54
    Cassette backup: CA 448
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 82, October 2, 1974, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 11, Reel 117)
    Work number: ubmu0063_117_01
    Constanten, Tom
    Greeting Blues/Sleet
    Performers: Unidentified
    Cassette backup: CA 449
    Work number: ubmu0063_117_02
    Sly/If you know, you know
    Duration: 12:27
    Cassette backup: CA 450
    Work number: ubmu0063_117_03
    Composer unknown
    Unidentified composition
    Cassette backup: CA 451
    Work number: ubmu0063_117_04
    Field, Wes
    Devil
    Duration: 10:07
    Cassette backup: CA 452
    Work number: ubmu0063_117_05
    Moon
    Performers: Tom Constanten, keyboards; Joel Perry, guitar; Murray Kohn, double bass; Dennis Whithanison, bass guitar; Art Levinowitz, soprano, alto and tenor saxophones; Albert Furness, drums; Doug Cameron, violin
    Duration: 16:58
    Cassette backup: CA 453
    Work number: ubmu0063_117_06
    Piano Rag
    Performers: Tom Constanten, piano
    Duration: 4:31
    Cassette backup: CA 454
    Work number: ubmu0063_117_07
    Great Green and Gold Take the Cakewalk
    Duration: 3:30
    Cassette backup: CA 455
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 83, November 6, 1974, 1 10-inch reel; Full-track mono, 7.5 ips (Box 11, Reel 118)
    Work number: ubmu0063_118_01
    Satie, Erik
    Vexations
    Performers: Claudia Hoca, Joseph Kubera, Stephen Manes, pianos
    Duration: 1:36:06
    Cassette backup: CA 456
    Note: Entire performance ran 6-12 p.m.; this recording captures 8-9:30. Check duration - insert states 1 ½ hours but cassette inventory states 30 minutes, but maybe that was all that was transferred to cassette.
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 84, January 22, 1975, 1 10-inch reel (Box 11) and 1 7-inch reel (Box 2); ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 11, 2, Reel 119-120)
    Work number: ubmu0063_119_01
    Camilleri, Charles
    Ritual Meditations
    Performers: Donald Knaack, gongos, congas, cymbals, tambourine
    Duration: 13:20
    Cassette backup: CA 457
    Work number: ubmu0063_119_02
    Steiner, Gitta
    Three pieces for Vibraphone Solo (1968)
    Performers: Donald Knaack, vibraphone
    Duration: 8:21
    Cassette backup: CA 458
    Work number: ubmu0063_119_03
    Knaack, Donald
    Reflections (1974)
    Performers: Donald Knaack, Dennis Kahle, percussion; Linda Swiniuch, choreography and dance
    Duration: 8:20
    Cassette backup: CA 459
    Work number: ubmu0063_119_04
    Liaisons (1968)
    Performers: Donald Knaack, marimba, vibraphone; tape realized by the composer
    Cassette backup: CA 460
    Work number: ubmu0063_119_05
    Coeur pour Batteur (1963)
    Performers: Donald Knaack, percussion and paper realization
    Duration: 5:20
    Cassette backup: CA 461
    Work number: ubmu0063_120_01
    Castaldi, Paolo
    Tendre Per un Esecutore (1961)
    Performers: Donald Knaack, percussion and vocalizations
    Duration: 20:10
    Cassette backup: CA 462
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 85, February 5, 1975, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 11, Reel 121-122)
    Work number: ubmu0063_121_01
    Schwartz, Elliott Shelling
    Soliloquies (1965)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Heather Johnson, clarinet; Benjamin Hudson, violin; Joseph Kubera, piano
    Duration: 14:50
    Cassette backup: CA 463
    Work number: ubmu0063_121_02
    Three Gymnopedies (1885)
    Cassette backup: CA 464
    Work number: ubmu0063_121_03
    Kirchner, Leon
    Sonata Concertante (1955)
    Duration: 21:33
    Cassette backup: CA 465
    Work number: ubmu0063_122_01
    Il cimento dell'armonia e dell'invenzione, op. 8, nos. 1-4 (Concerti delle stagioni)
    Performers: Benjamin Hudson, solo violin; Carol Zeavin, Jon Shallit, Douglas Cone, Michael Rosenbloom, Keiko Yamasaki, violins; Maureen Gallagher, Laurie Kennedy, violas; Dana Rusinak, violoncello; James Van der Mark, double bass; Joseph Kubera, harpsichord
    Duration: 48:32
    Cassette backup: CA 466
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 86, March 6, 1975, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 11, Reel 123)
    Work number: ubmu0063_123_01
    Martin, Judith Lynn
    Syzygy (1973)
    Performers: Judith Martin, synket
    Cassette backup: CA 467
    Work number: ubmu0063_123_02
    Parlore pieces (1972)
    Performers: Judith Martin, mini-moog
    Duration: 7:17
    Cassette backup: CA 468
    Work number: ubmu0063_123_03
    Sonora Borealis (1971)
    Duration: 10:56
    Cassette backup: CA 469
    Work number: ubmu0063_123_04
    Jandl, Ernst
    Devil Trap
    Performers: Judith Martin, voice
    Cassette backup: CA 470
    Work number: ubmu0063_123_05
    Improvisation
    Sign
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Benjamin Hudson, violin; Joseph Kubera, piano; Donald Knaack, percussion; Judith Martin, synket; Sandra Reher, photography; Ralph Jones, sound engineer
    Duration: 22:19
    Cassette backup: CA 471
    Engineer's note: "Silent portion at circa 5:00 to ca. 12:00" - continue transfer throughout
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 87, April 16, 1975, 1 10-inch reel (Box 11) and 1 7-inch reel (Box 2); ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 11, 2, Reel 124-125)
    Work number: ubmu0063_124_01
    Yun, Isang
    Etudes (1974)
    Duration: 18:11
    Cassette backup: CA 472
    Work number: ubmu0063_124_02
    Fritsch, Johannes Georg
    Sul g (1970)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, piccolo, flute; Joseph Kubera, piano
    Duration: 11:10
    Cassette backup: CA 473
    Work number: ubmu0063_124_03
    Scherchen, Tona
    Sin (1967)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Jan Williams, percussion
    Cassette backup: CA 474
    Work number: ubmu0063_124_04
    Kadha Karuna (1962)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Joseph Kubera, piano
    Duration: 8:41
    Cassette backup: CA 475